LOGAN ALLEN

(770) 503-5494 loganallc@gmail.com

EMPLOYMENT

Co-founder, Software Developer

Slingput

August 2014 - Current

- Developing a web app for creating beautiful landing pages as a part of Startup x Month.
- Using Ruby on Rails and AngularJS.

Software Development Intern

Gather Technologies

June 2014 - Current

- Rewrote private events management web app for restaurants in AngularJS.
- Redesigned marketing site, implemented responsive design for mobile, and improved SEO.
- Wrote automated testing suite using Karma and Protractor.

Software Development Intern

TripLingo

January - May 2014

- Reimagined TripLingo's app through JavaScript and Appcelerator Titanium for translation in an emergency room context.
- Delved into user experience of doctors and patients, and created a streamlined app for iPads.

Front-end Development Intern

BestFit Mobile

April - December 2013

- Led front-end development to create an app for Fresenius Medical Care, a company with 55,000 employees that allows doctors to refer patients to other doctors.
- Developed a conference room booking app using **Sencha Touch** for internal use.

SIDE PROJECTS

- Docket App (April 2014). Created a web app for presenting upcoming events that integrated with Google Calendar and utilized canvas. Featured in Access North Georgia and the Gainesville Times. JavaScript.
- Clerk App (Fall 2013). Android news app that allowed users to directly reward authors for quality articles through micro-donations. Java, NodeJS.

EDUCATION

Atlanta, GA

Georgia Institute of Technology

Fall 2014 - Current

Computer Science major - Graduating May 2018 (Expected)

Skills

JavaScript, Java, HTML, CSS, Design, Prototyping, SH, SQL, Python, Ruby on Rails, Testing

Bio

Design-oriented by nature, I focus on front-end development and user experience, leveraging my passion for the open web to craft beautiful web apps and sites.

A builder at heart, I am a self-starter whose passion shows in everything I do. I love diving into new technologies and am able to quickly familiarize myself with large codebases to begin contributing.